<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sample</string>
    <string name="sample">Hi, I\'m Donald Trump, president of the United States of America. C\'mon ask me some questions. Together we can MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN!</string>
    <string-array name="samples">
        <item>"Hi, welcome to Crown! I’m Lucy, your virtual concierge. I’m here to answer all your questions and help you navigate your way around. Got a question about the restaurants, hotels or entertainment at Crown? No problem! Use the microphone button to ask me a question directly or tap the 'WHAT CAN I ASK' button."</item>
        <item>"Crown is open 24 hours a day, 7 days a week except on the following days: Christmas Day, Good Friday and Anzac Day."</item>
        <item>"Crown Casino Melbourne operates 24 hours a day, 7 days a week with the exception of Christmas Day, Good Friday and ANZAC Day. On these days Crown is closed rom 4am and re opens 12 noon."</item>
        <item>"Crown Entertainment Complex is located on 8 Whiteman St, Southbank Melbourne. Crown Perth is located at Great Eastern Highway, Burswood Perth."</item>
        <item>"Valet parking is available at the Casino Atrium Entrance - Whiteman Street. The cost is $55 per 24-hours period. Payment is on exit. All prices include GST. Parking rates are subject to change."</item>
        <item>"At Crown we offer a diverse range of restaurants to cater to your every taste! Our restaurants range from premium for a complete dining experience to casual for a more relaxed atmosphere and a range of quick-bite restaurants for when you are on the go!"</item>
        <item>"We have three five-star luxury hotels at Crown Melbourne. You can choose to stay at either Crown Towers, Crown Metropol or Crown Promenade."</item>
        <item>"Every hour from 9:00pm to midnight on weekdays, and from 8:00pm to Midnight on weekends."</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="samples2">
        <item>丫米丫米,我最喜欢吃这个了,谢谢你.</item>
        <item>想和我打拳击吗?让你见识一下我的厉害吧.</item>
        <item>我生气的时候可是会踢人的哦,你可要小心点.</item>
        <item>哎呀,我不喜欢吃这个.</item>
        <item>喜欢我的帽子吗?你可以在卡片收藏夹里购买哦.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>